Register of the National Republic records, 1918-1960
Hoover Institution Archives
- Information File A (Boxes 1-398)
  - Steward, Maxwell S.
  - St, miscellaneous
  - Stone, I.F.
  - Stimson, Henry Lewis
  - Stokes, Rose Pastor
  - Strikes
  - Striking Miners Relief Committee
  - Strikes-Striking Committees
  - Strikes-Pacific Coast
  - Spanish Civil War
    - Dies Expose
    - U.S. Neutrality and Embargo Legislation
    - Issues in U.S. (Box 325)
    - Government
    - Post War
    - Civil War
    - Pre-War (Box 326)
  - Spanish Aid
    - Loyalist Recruits
    - Movements
    - Abraham Lincoln Brigade, Friends of
    - Movements-Medical Bureau to Aid Spanish Democracy
    - Movements-American Friends of Spanish Democracy [2 folders]
    - Movements-Washington Friends of Spanish Democracy Loyalist Supporters (Box 327)
    - Movements-American Society for Technical Aid to Spanish Democracy
    - Movements-North American Committee to Aid Spanish Democracy
    - State Department Reports
  - Sti, miscellaneous (Box 328)
  - Supreme Court
    - General
    - Black appointment
    - Decisions
    - New Deal Attacks on
    - Addresses on
    - Justice
    - Proposed Reorganization
    - Opposition to Proposed Reorganization (Box 329)
  - Sweden
  - Switzerland
  - Su, miscellaneous
  - Soviet Russia (Box 330)
    - Agriculture
    - Armaments
    - Army
    - Art
    - Atwater
    - Bargeron
    - Beal
    - Costello
    - Douillet ("Moscow Unveiled")
    - Duranty
    - Erastus
    - Kravchenko, Victor
    - Articles in Spanish
    - Lang
    - Lovett
    - Sanger (Box 331)
    - Smith
    - Snegoff
    - Tchernavin
    - Miscellaneous articles [2 folders]
    - Atheism (Box 332)
    - Atheistic cartoons
    - Aviation
    - Books on
    - Blood Money B. Coan
    - Catholic Church
    - Celebrations
    - Communist Party
    - Culture (Box 333)
    - Economics
      - General
      - Articles
      - Literature
    - Espionage
    - Embassy, U.S.
    - Financial (Box 334)
    - Five Year Plan
    - Foreign Relations
      - General
      - General (Box 335)
      - Austria
      - Baltic States
      - Bulgaria
      - China
      - Czechoslovakia
      - Finland
      - France
      - Germany
      - Great Britain (Box 336)
      - England
      - Iran
      - Italy
      - Japan
      - Poland
      - Rumania
      - Spain
      - Sweden
      - Turkey
      - United States [3 folders] (Box 337)
      - Yugoslavia (Box 338)
      - Leaders
    - General
    - Government
    - Industrial (Box 339)
    - Labor
    - Purges
    - Lenin
    - Troyanovsky, Alex
    - Litvinoff, Maxim
    - Letters
    - Literature
    - O.G.P.U.
    - Opposition (Box 340)
    - Political
    - Posters
    - Propaganda
    - Refugees
    - Social
    - Stalin
    - Taxation (Box 341)
    - Third (Communist) International
      - General [2 folders]
      - Clippings
    - Tours
    - Trade
      - Foreign
      - General
      - Great Britain (Box 342)
      - Knickerbocker articles
      - Investments
      - Religion
      - U.S.
    - U.S. (Box 343)
    - Trials and executions
    - Women
    - Youth
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets
    - Recognition (Box 344)
      - Opposition to [2 folders]
      - Endorsers of
      - Literature [2 folders] (Box 345)
      - Pre-recognition [2 folders] (Box 346)
  - Timone, George A.
  - Thanksgiving
  - Tool Owners Union
  - Tagore, Sir Rabindranath
  - Tamiment
  - Tariff
    - General
    - Lockwood Articles
    - Clippings
    - Literature (Box 347)
  - Taxation
    - Clippings
    - Income Tax
    - Literature (Box 348)
  - Taylor, Glen Hearst
  - Tenants and Tenants League
  - Time Magazine
  - Tobias, Channing
  - Thyssen, Fritz
  - Technocracy (Box 349)
  - T, miscellaneous
  - Thatcher, Thomas D.
  - Third Parties
    - General
    - Clippings
    - Labor
    - LaFollette Party (Box 350)
  - Tolstoy, Leo (Family)
  - Townsend Plan
  - Town Hall of Washington
  - Thompson, Dorothy
  - Thomas, Elbert D.
  - Threefold Movement
  - Th, miscellaneous
  - Town Hall Committee of Wichita, Kansas
  - Teachers' organizations (Box 351)
    - General
    - American Education Fellowship
    - American Federation of Teachers [2 folders]
    - American Progressive Education
    - American Educational Fellowship
  - Teachers' Oath (Literature) (Box 352)
  - Teachers
    - Union
    - Radical
    - Radical (Box 353)
    - Radical (Box 354)
    - Coudert-Rapp Committee
    - Pacifist
    - Professors
      - General
      - Brooklyn College, NY
      - City College NY
      - Dr. Harry Elmer Barnes
      - Dr. Charles A. Beard
      - Dr. Franz Boaz
      - George S. Counts
      - Davis, Jerome, Prof.
      - Dewey, John, Prof. (Box 355)
      - Douglas, Paul H.
      - Columbia University
      - Literature
      - Ezekiel, Mordecai, Prof.
      - Gellerman, William
      - Henderson, Donald
      - Hicks, Granville
      - Hoover, Calvin B.
      - Hudson, Manley O.
      - Langford, Howard D.
      - Lasswell, Harold
      - Lindeman, Eduard C.
      - Lynd, Robert S.
      - May, Kenneth
      - Meiklejohn, Prof. Alexander
      - Miller, Herbert A., Prof.
      - Mitchell, Broadus
      - Newlon, Jesse H.
      - Ogburn, W. F.
      - Rugg, Harold
      - Russell, Bertrand
      - Schappes, Morris U.
      - Schuman, Frederick L.
      - Watson, Goodwin
      - Shotwell, James T.
  - Tresca, Carlo (Box 356)
  - Trotsky, Leon
  - Treason
  - Truman, H. S. (See also New Deal)
  - Tugwell, Bill
  - Turkey
  - Two Party System (Box 357)
  - Tr, miscellaneous
  - Ukraine
  - Ukraine-Russia Civic Center
  - Unemployment
    - General
    - Literature
  - Unemployment Councils (Box 358)
  - Unemployment Insurance
  - National Congress for Unemployment Insurance
  - Union for Democratic Action
    - General
    - Clippings
  - Union League of Michigan
  - U.S. Board of Trade (Box 359)
  - Union Now (Federal Union Inc.)
    - General [2 folders]
    - Clippings
  - Union to Preserve American Ideals and Institutions
  - United Brotherhood of Washington
  - United China Relief, Inc.
  - United Christian Council for Democracy
  - United Committee for South Slavic America
  - United Nations (Box 360)
    - Army
    - UNRRA
    - Food Conference
    - After 10 Years
    - Charter
    - Charter revision (Box 361)
    - Flag
    - Foreign countries
    - God, U.N. and
    - Human rights
    - International Criminal Court
    - International Law Committee
    - Korea
    - Military
    - Miscellaneous
    - One World and world government
    - Participation act (Box 362)
    - Personnel
      - Russia
      - Foreign countries
      - First loyalty of employees
      - Grand jury and Acheson hearing
      - Probes of U.N. by various agencies
      - Reds in U.N (general)
      - State Department
      - Subversive personnel
      - Subversives helped by Hiss and three Senators
      - Subversives, eleven U.S. employees dismissed
      - Women
    - Refugees
    - Russia
    - Schools
    - U.S. Constitution and U.N.
    - World Health Organization
  - U.N. Day (Box 363)
    - World U.N.
    - Organization
      - General
      - Clippings
    - Human Rights Commission
    - UNESCO [2 folders]
    - UNESCO [3 folders] (Box 364)
    - UNICEF
  - United World Federalists [3 folders] (Box 365)
  - United World Federalists [3 folders] (Box 366)
  - United World Federalists. Literature (Box 367)
    - General
    - World Government News
  - Uruguay
  - Utopianism, Utopian Society
  - U, miscellaneous
  - Valtin, Jan (Box 368)
  - Van Paassen, Pierre
  - Venezuela
  - Versailles, Treaty of
  - Veterans
    - General
      - General
      - A-B
      - C-D
      - F-I
      - M-T
      - V
      - U-Y
    - Organizations
      - General
      - American League of Ex-Servicemen (Box 369)
      - International Veterans (U.N.)
      - American Legion
        - General [2 folders]
        - General [2 folders] (Box 370)
        - Summary of trends and developments
        - UNESCO (Box 371)
      - American Veterans Association, Inc.
      - American Veterans Committee
      - American Vets of World War II (AMVETS)
      - Christian Veterans of America
      - Disabled American Veterans (DAV)
      - Catholic War Veterans (Box 372)
      - National Conference of Union Labor Legionnaires
      - Protestant War Veterans
      - Regular Veterans Association
      - Vets' Committee Against Discrimination
      - Vets' National Rank and File Committee
      - VFW, Veterans of Foreign Wars
      - VFW, Literature
      - Workers' Ex-Servicemen League (Box 373)
      - Veterans' Publications, World War II
      - United Negro and Allied Veterans of America
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison
  - Voorhis, H. Jerry
  - V, miscellaneous
  - Wagner, Robert L.
  - Walker, James J. (Mayor)
  - Wallace, Henry A., 1946
  - Wallace, Henry A. (Box 374)
    - Secretary of Agriculture
    - For President Movement
    - Vice President
    - Nomination for Secretary of Commerce Controversy
    - Secretary of Commerce
  - Walsh, Frank P., Secretary of Commerce
  - Walsh, Thomas J. (Sen.)
  - W, miscellaneous (Box 375)
  - War
  - World War I [not all materials]
  - World War II
    - General
    - France
    - Germany
    - Great Britain
    - Italy
    - Japan
    - Russia (Box 376)
    - United States
    - Conferences
    - Conferences (Box 377)
    - Conferences, Bretton Woods
    - Conferences, Dumbarton Oaks
  - Washington Committee for Democratic Action
  - Washington Commonwealth Federation
  - Washington Open Forum
  - Washington, George [2 folders] (Box 378)
  - Washington Post
  - Wam, miscellaneous
  - Wells, H. G. (Box 379)
  - Welsh, Francis Ralston
  - We, miscellaneous
  - Whalen, Grover
  - Wheat (Wheat Conference)
  - Wheeler, Burton K. (Sen.)
  - White, William Allen
  - White Russians
  - Whitney, R.M.
  - Wh, miscellaneous
  - Wickersham Commission (Box 380)
  - Wickersham, George
  - Wi, miscellaneous
  - Willkie, Wendell L.
  - Wilkinson, Ellen
  - Wilson, Woodrow
  - Wil, miscellaneous
  - Winchell, Walter (Box 381)
  - Wirt, William A., Dr. [2 folders]
  - War Department (Box 382)
  - War Police Commission
  - War debts
    - General
    - Great Britain
    - Articles-Addresses
    - Anglo-French Alliance
    - European Coference
    - France
    - Germany
    - Moratorium
  - Women (Box 383)
    - General [2 folders]
    - Abbott, Grace
    - Addams, Jane
    - Benedict, Ruth
    - Day, Dorothy
    - Douglas, Helen Gahagan (Box 384)
    - Hurst, Fannie
    - Ilma, Viola
    - Miller, Frieda S.
    - Smedley, Agnes
    - Utley, Freda
    - Van Kleeck, Mary
    - Waters, Agnes
    - Woolley, Mary Emma
    - Strong, Anna Louise
      - General
      - A-E
      - F-I
      - M
      - N
      - O-Z except U
      - W
  - Women's organizations (Box 385)
    - World Congress of Women
    - National Council of Women of U.S.
    - American Women's Association
    - Congress of American Women and Women's International Democratic Federation [same folder]
    - General Federations of Womens Clubs
    - League of Women Voters
    - League of Women Shoppers
    - League of Mothers' Organizations (Box 386)
    - National Council of Federal Church Women
    - National Women's Party
    - National Women's Trade Union League
    - United Conference Against High Cost of Living
    - Women's Constitutional League
    - Women Investors in America, Inc.
    - Womens Publications
    - Woman Patriot
    - Women's Patriotic Conference on National Defense [2 folders]
  - Workers' organizations (Box 387)
  - Workers' Alliance (WPA Investment Committee Report)
  - Workers' Alliance
    - Clippings
    - Dies Committee Expose
    - National Right-to-Work
    - Work Congress
    - Conventions, marches, etc. in Washington, D.C.
  - Workers' Defense League (Box 388)
  - Workers' International Relief
  - World Affairs Council
  - Wo, miscellaneous
  - World Alliance for International Friendship through Churches
  - World Court
    - General
    - General (Box 389)
    - Address on
    - Articles
    - Anti-World Court
    - Pro-World Court
    - Clippings
    - National Committee
  - World Fellowship of Faiths
  - World Government
    - General
    - General (Box 390)
    - State Legislative Action
    - World Trade Union Conference and World Federation of Trade Unions
    - Atlantic Union (Committee)
    - Americans United for World Organization, Inc.
    - American Association for the United Nations, Inc.
    - General. Clippings
  - World Government, Literature (Box 391)
  - World Neighbors [2 folders]
  - World Tomorrow
  - World Revolution
  - Writers War Board (Box 392)
  - Y, miscellaneous
  - Young Life Campaign
  - Young, Owen D.
  - Youth
  - Youth, A Study, Muncie, Indiana, 1938
  - Youth organizations (Box 393)
    - General
    - Literature
    - Allied Youth, Inc.
    - American Youth Congress
      - General
      - General (Box 394)
      - National Republic report
      - Clippings
      - First Congress
      - Citizenship Institute, D.C.
      - Washington Youth Council (Box 395)
      - Citizens' Institute, D.C., Feb. 1940
      - American Youth Act
      - Pamphlets
    - American Youth for a Free World
    - American Youth for a World Youth
    - Association of Christian Youth Movements
    - Boys' Republic - Girls' Republic
    - National Foundation for American Youth
    - World Youth Council and World Youth Conference
    - World Federation of Democratic Youth (Box 396)
    - National Youth Assembly Against UMT
    - Oklahoma Youth Legislation
    - United Christian Youth Movement
    - Pioneer Youth of America
    - World Youth Conference - First
    - World Youth Peace Congress
    - YMCA
    - YMCA (Box 397)
    - YMCA-YWCA
    - Youth Councils
    - Youth Builders
    - Youth for Christ International
  - Youth delinquincy
  - Youth hostels (Box 398)
  - Yugoslavia
  - Z, miscellaneous
- American Legion Selected Documents, 1940-1959 (Boxes 399-403)
  Correspondence and printed matter collected by the American Legion, arranged in consecutively numbered folders. Box 399 contains a partial index.
  - Index to Books 1-6 (Box 399)
  - Index to Books 7-9, 12
  - Book 1 (Box 400)
  - Book 2
  - Book 3
  - Book 4 (Box 401)
  - Book 5
  - Book 6
  - Book 7 (Box 402)
  - Book 8
  - Book 9
  - Book 10 (Box 403)
  - Book 11
  - Book 12
- National Republic Bulletins, Lettergrams, and Weekly Letters, 1950-1958 (Boxes 404-406)
  Bulletins, lettergrams, and weekly letters, arranged as listed. Box 404 contains an index to the lettergrams.
  - Bulletin, 1950 January - 1951 September (Box 404)
  - Lettergrams
    - Index
    - Nos. 1-133
    - Nos. 133-277 (Box 405)
  - Weekly Letters
    - 1949-1952
    - 1953 (Box 406)
    - 1955
    - 1956
    - 1958
- Subject File on Communism, 1930-1950 (Boxes 416-436)
  Newspaper clippings and printed matter about communism, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Anti-communism (Box 416)
  - Anti-red actions - states
  - Anti-red legislation
  - Anti-U.S.
  - Art (Box 417)
  - Attacks against Congressional committees
  - Books
  - Bookshops - communist
  - Books on communism
  - Brownell and anti-red laws
  - Cain
  - Communism, general
  - Communism in religion
  - Communism in U.S.
  - Communist (Box 418)
    - Activities - states
    - Camps
    - Culture
    - Discipline
    - Force and violence
    - International
    - Membership
    - Men
    - Oath
    - Organizations
    - Party (Box 419)
    - Party vs. Subversive Activities Control Board
    - Propaganda
    - Publications
    - Ranches
    - Revolution in U.S.
    - Schools (Box 420)
    - Tactics
    - Threats
    - Trials
    - Underground
    - Women
    - Youth
  - Contempt
  - Court cases
  - Culture - miscellaneous (Box 421)
  - Curbs on Reds
  - Danger of communism
  - Definitions of communism
  - D.C. Reds
  - Eastland Committee
  - "8" Reds
  - "11" Reds
  - Ex-reds
  - Federal housing oaths
  - "15" Reds
  - Fifth Amendment
  - "5" Reds
  - "14" Reds
  - Fronts
  - Hennings Committee (Box 422)
  - Hollywood men
  - Hollywood "10"
  - Hollywood women
  - Informers
  - Jenner and Grouzenko
  - Loyalty
  - Loyalty oaths
  - Movies (Box 423)
  - Music and records
  - Orders from Moscow
  - Outlawing of reds
  - Party Affairs (periodical)
  - Pittsburgh raid
  - Probes
    - General
    - Hollywood
    - Maryland (Box 424)
    - Michigan
    - New Hampshire
    - New York
    - Oregon
    - Seattle
    - West Coast
  - Pumpkin papers
  - Radio - T.V.
  - Red finances
  - Red lawyers
  - Red leaders
  - Red newspapermen
  - Reds in (Box 425)
    - Army and Navy
    - Churches
    - Government
    - Movies
    - Senate committee
    - South
    - State Department
  - Reds plan war on U.S.
  - Reece, B. Carroll
  - Registration of reds
  - Risks (Box 426)
  - Sabotage
  - Scientists and security
  - Secret press
  - Secret radios
  - Security
  - Security files
  - "7" Reds
  - "17" Reds
  - "6" Reds
  - "16" Reds
  - Smith Act
  - Sorge
  - Soviet U.S.A. (Box 427)
  - Spies
  - Spy ring
  - Subersive Activities Control Board
  - Subversives
  - Television - radio - stage
  - Testify under immunity
  - U.S. Army and reds
  - U.S. in war with Russia
  - U.S. reds - tools of Russia
  - World movement
  - World revolution
  - Miscellaneous, unorganized (Box 428-436)
- Information File B (Boxes 437-714)
  Newspaper clippings, pamphlets, printed matter, and reports, arranged alphabetically by subject. General letter folders in this series may also contain data on organizations, individuals, and subjects identified in Information Files A and C.
  - A (Box 437)
  - Ab
  - Abraham Lincoln Brigade
  - Ac
  - Acheson (Box 438)
  - Ad
  - Adams, Sherman
  - Adler, Larry
  - Adult Leadership
  - Advertising Council
  - Aerospace [2 folders]
  - Aerospace (Box 439)
  - Af - Ag
  - Ai
  - Aim
    - General [3 folders]
    - Association of Interns and Medical Students (Box 440)
    - Committee for International Student Cooperation
    - International Union of Students
    - Student organizations
  - Al [4 folders] (Box 441)
  - Alaska
  - Aliens (Box 442)
    - General
    - Immigration [3 folders]
    - Immigration [5 folders] (Box 443)
    - Immigration [3 folders] (Box 444)
    - McCarran
    - Struve, Col. Charles B.
  - All-American Conference
  - Allis-Chalmers
  - Am [5 folders] (Box 445)
  - Am [5 folders] (Box 446)
  - Am [5 folders] (Box 447)
  - Amerasia (Box 448)
  - American-Asian Educational Exchange
  - American Bar Association [2 folders]
  - American Civil Liberties Union [4 folders]
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 449-452)
  - American Coalition (Box 453)
  - American Council of Churches
  - American Enterprise Association
  - American Friends of Czechoslovakia
  - American Heritage Protective Committee
  - American Legion (pamphlets)
  - American Legion (Box 454-464)
  - American Nationalist (Box 465)
  - American Public Relations Forum
  - Americans for Constitutional Action
  - Americans for Democratic Action [5 folders]
  - Americans for Democratic Action [5 folders] (Box 466)
  - Americans for MacArthur (Box 467)
  - Americans United for World Organization Inc.
  - American Unitarian Youth
  - American Youth for Democracy
  - American Youth for a Free World
  - America's Future, Inc.
  - Amtorg
  - An
  - Anti-communist literature [5 folders] (Box 468)
  - Ap (Box 469)
  - Ar [2 folders]
  - Armed services [4 folders]
  - Armed services [4 folders] (Box 470)
  - As [2 folders]
  - As [3 folders] (Box 471)
  - Asian People's Anti-Communist League of Republic of China
  - At
  - Atheism
  - Atlantic Charter
  - Atlantic Union
  - Atomic energy [3 folders] (Box 472)
  - Atomic Energy Commission [3 folders]
  - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 473-475)
  - Atomic Energy Commission [2 folders] (Box 476)
  - Au
  - Automation
  - Automobile industry
  - Aviation
  - Aware Inc.
  - Axis Sally
  - Ay
  - B [2 folders]
  - B (Box 477)
  - Ba [2 folders]
  - Baruch, Bernard
  - Be [2 folders]
  - Be (Box 478)
  - Beall, Jack
  - Beck, Dave
  - Belfrage, Cedric
  - Best, Robert
  - Bi
  - Bible
  - Bibliographies [2 folders]
  - Bibliographies (Box 479)
    - General
    - Book clubs
  - Bilbo, Theodore
  - Bill of Rights
  - Bill of Rights Conference
  - Birinyi, Louis K.
  - Birth control
  - Bittelman, Alexander
  - Bl
  - Black Dragon Society
  - Bo (Box 480)
  - Br
  - Bra
  - Brasol, Boris
  - Bre
  - Bricker, John W. (Box 481)
  - Bridge, Sen. Styles
  - British groups in the U.S.A.
  - Bro
  - Browder, Earl
  - Brownells, Sam Herb
  - Bu
  - Bu (Box 482)
  - Budenz, Louis
  - Budget, federal
  - Bullitt, William C.
  - Bunche, Ralph C.
  - By
  - C
  - C (Box 483)
  - C (Box 484)
  - Ca
  - Cain, Harry P.
  - Cal
  - Cam
  - Capehart, Homer E.
  - Capitalism
  - Capitol
  - Care
  - Carr, Edward H. (Box 485)
  - Carr, Sam
  - Cartoons
  - Cas (Box 486)
  - Cat
  - Cause and cure of war
  - Ce
  - Central Intelligence Agency
  - Ch
  - Ch (Box 487)
  - Chamber of Commerce
  - Chambers, Whittaker (Box 488)
  - Chaplin, Charles
  - Charts
  - China lobby
  - Christmas, anti
  - Christian Forum
  - Christoffel, Harold
  - Christophers
  - Churches
    - General
    - General (Box 489-492)
    - Catholic (Box 493)
    - Methodist
    - Methodist (Box 494)
  - Ci
  - C.I.O. Veterans Committee
  - Citizens' Committee for Hoover Report
  - Citizens' councils
  - Citizens for Victory (Box 495)
  - Citizens' Foreign Relations Committee
  - Citizenship (Box 496)
  - Civil defense
  - Civil Liberties Clearing House
  - Civil rights
  - Civil Rights Congress (Box 497)
  - Civil service
  - Civil war
  - Cl
  - Co
  - Co (Box 498)
  - Coexistence
  - Com
  - Com (Box 499)
  - Comic books
  - Commager, Henry Steele
  - Commerce, Department of
  - Committee for Economic Development
  - Committe for National Trade Policy
  - Committee of One Million
  - Committee for World Development and World Disarmament
  - Common Sense
  - Communism
    - General
    - General (Box 500-508)
    - General (Box 509)
    - Arizona
    - Armed forces
    - Atomic bomb
    - Atomic bomb [5 folders] (Box 510)
    - Atomic bomb [5 folders] (Box 511)
    - Congress (Box 512)
    - House Committee on Un-American Activities
    - International
    - Mexican labor
    - Motion picture industry [3 folders]
    - Propaganda methods (Box 513)
    - Texas
  - Communist
    - Espionage [2 folders]
    - International
      - General
      - 6th World Congress
    - Movies
    - Party
    - Party pamphlets
    - Party pamphlets (Box 514-516)
    - Trials [2 folders] (Box 517)
  - Community chests
  - Compulsory health insurance
  - Con [3 folders]
  - Condon, Dr. Edward U. (Box 518)
  - Condon, John A.
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion
  - Congress [2 folders]
  - Congress of Freedom Inc.
  - Conscientious objectors
  - Constitution
  - Constitution (Box 519)
  - Consumers Research Union
  - Cooperatives
  - Cooperatives (Box 520)
  - Cou
  - Cr
  - Crouch, Paul (Box 521)
  - Crusade for Freedom
  - Cu
  - Cv
  - D
  - D (Box 522)
  - D (Box 523)
  - D.A.
  - Daughters of the American Revolution
  - De
  - De (Box 524)
  - Defenders of the American Constitution
  - Defense Department
  - Democrats [4 folders]
  - Democrats [2 folders] (Box 525)
  - Di
  - Dies Committee (see also boxes 774-775)
  - Djilas, Milovan
  - Do
  - Dodd, William E.
  - Douglas, William O. (Justice) (Box 526)
  - Dr
  - Draper, Paul
  - Du [2 folders]
  - Dw [2 folders]
  - E
  - E (Box 527)
  - Eastland, James O.
  - Eaton, Cyrus
  - Ebey, George W.
  - Ec
  - Ec (Box 528)
  - Eccles, M. S.
  - Economic Cooperation Administration
  - Economy
  - Education
    - General [4 folders]
    - General (Box 529-536)
    - Federal Aid (Box 537)
    - Investigations [2 folders]
  - Edison, Mrs. Charles
  - Einstein [2 folders]
  - Eisenhower, D. D. [2 folders]
  - Eisenhower, D. D. [4 folders] (Box 538)